{
    "id": "cedc89bc9fc3468a93f4e18ff12900ce",
    "title": "Past simple or present perfect tense?",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "13459c80063f48e4a26cc1fef2ff0d0e",
            "title": "Past Simple Or Present Perfect Tense",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When ………………… from work?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did she return",
                        "did she returned",
                        "has she returned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… to the US?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did you ever go",
                        "Have you ever been",
                        "Did you ever been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is the most beautiful woman ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I had ever seen",
                        "I have ever seen",
                        "I have ever saw"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is the best movie …………………… ..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I ever watched",
                        "I have ever watched",
                        "I did ever watch"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is the most difficult problem …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I ever had to deal with",
                        "I have ever had to deal with",
                        "I had to deal with",
                        "I ever dealt with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When …………………. I was working in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you phoned",
                        "have phoned",
                        "had phoned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… with children before, so I know what to expect in my new job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have worked",
                        "worked",
                        "had worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. all my childhood in France.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "spent",
                        "have spent",
                        "had spent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who …………………… that necklace?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "gave you",
                        "has given you",
                        "had given you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There …………………. a plane crash near Bristol last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "has been",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}